Contact

Address 1: Duhok

Address 2: Erbil

Email:

f1c3you@gmail.com

Mob: 07508761306

Top Skills

- MS Offices | Very Good
- Python | Very Good
- SQL | Very Good
- Unity | Very Good
- Android | Good
- Data Warehousing | Good
- C# | Very Good
- Arduino | Very Good
- Computer Opt. | Very Good

Rasan Diyar Tayeb

To be intelligent you need knowledge.

Summary:

Focused on my objectives in the field of my job. Pursuit my goals in life, make the best out of myself for the team that I am working with or firm. Graduated from Duhok Polytechnic University, with 6+ years of work experience in (data entry, data manipulation, data analyzing, laboring, communicating, inspecting, and solving problems). Aiming to leverage a proven knowledge of my skills to successfully fill the needs at your firm. Frequently praised as Proactive by my peers. I can be relied upon to help the company achieve its goals.

Languages

Kurdish | Native

English | Excellent

Arabic | Very Good

French | Basic

Certificates

Data Analyst for Enterprise

Business Analytics Nanodegree

SQL for data science

TOT

<u>ICT</u>

Volunteer job

Cybersecurity by CISCO

Human Resource

Scientific Conference

Tech in Co Newroz University

OpenLearn data analysis

SQL for data analysis

Business Intelligence Analyst

Education

Duhok Polytechnic University

Department of Information Technology Management

1st Year (2017-2018)

Some of my subjects were:

IT Fundamentals | Very Good

Management Principles | Very Good

English Language | Very Good

C++ | Excellent

Principles of Statistics | Good

Principles of Accounting | Pass

2nd Year (2018-2019)

Some of my subjects were:

Object Oriented Programming | Very Good

Data Structure | Fair

Management Information System | Fair

Java | Very Good

Production and Operation Information

Systems | Pass

Cost Accounting

Education

Duhok Polytechnic University

Department of Information Technology Management

3rd Year (2019-2020)

Some of my subjects were:

Database system Oracle | Good

Network and Communication | Very Good

System Analysis and Design | Good

Financial Management | Fair

C# | Fair

Operating System | Very Good

Web Development | Fair

4th Year (2020-2021)

Some of my subjects were:

Artificial Intelligence | Fair

Information security | Very Good

Data Warehousing | Good

Mobile Technology | Excellent

Decision Support System | Fair

Experience

New Standard

Laborer/Inspector

Worked as a truck/vehicle inspector at the Zakho customs.

My job was to make sure nothing illegal enters the borders of the Kurdistan region.

I was also responsible for taking out samples from the trucks that was caring cosmetic products, cleaning products and inhaling products to the inspection area.

As an IT support specialist, I had to work on two types of computers, one of them was for entering vehicle and driver data, general data about the product and its destination, the second computer was for entering samples data.

My shift was every two days, one day for (24hrs).

Programs that I worked on were (Excel, C# and Word).

July 2017 - August 2017 (2 months)

Experience

UNICEF project

Volunteering for UNICEF project

UNICEF gave us a training for three days, the first day was about helping and giving with what you have and out instructor talked about 'mother Teresa' and how she helped people in India.

The second day was about leadership and team work, also how to be motivated, trust your friend, solve problems and (ego, alter ego and superego).

The final day was about Kurdistan problems and what we want as future generation.

After the training they gave us certificates.

And they told us to give lessons to an education center so a group of us went to 'Rand Private Institute' and gave its students lessons about leadership, trust, friendship, parenting.... etc.

October 21/2021

Experience

Be Best Company

Promotions Manager

I was the HR officer who gathered and recruited instructors, teachers, and professional trainers to give courses at our company.

I was also responsible for promoting and marketing our company which was my top priority.

June 2015 - August 2017 (2 years 3 months)

Rand Institute (Click here...)

Teacher

I taught subjects like (SQL, Linux Terminal, IT, Windows, and Server back-end) for grades (1, 3, and 4).

I was also a member of the Exam Committee for the whole year.

October 19/2021 – June 1/2022 (1 year)